lerablog.org 2019-04-01

# Privacy policy - Lera Blog

We value the privacy and security of the information that you share with us. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, share, protect and process your information. Any information that you provide to us is used strictly to process and fulfill your purchase and/or for internal analytical purposes, as described in this Privacy Policy. We only share information for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, and we will not sell or redistribute any of your information to any third party. We use commercially reasonable efforts to protect your information from unauthorized disclosure. We may use the information from your order to process your purchase, provide a refund, provide customer service, improve or customize our products and services or fulfill applicable financial, tax, legal or compliance requirements.

**How We Obtain Personal Data**

When browsing this web site, the IP used to access the site will be logged in addition to the dates and times of connection. This information is purely utilized to study trends, manage the blog, track visitors activity and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Above all, any saved IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable data.

**Third Party Links**

We may feature hyperlinks on this web site for your reference. We cannot be held responsible for the privacy policies, or lack there of, on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these web sites may differ from our own.

**Log Files**

Like most standard websites, our website uses log files. These include: Internet Protocol addresses (IP addresses), browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and the number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc., are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Web Cookies and Beacons**

Web cookies (also known as HTTP cookies, or just cookies) are parcels of text that are sent by a server to a Web browser, and then sent back unchanged by the browser each time it accesses that server. In other words, a cookie is a piece of data stored on a user’s computer that is tied to information about the user.

Web beacons are objects that are embedded in a webpage or email that are invisible to the user, but allow checking that a user has viewed the page or email. Other names are web bug, tracking bug, tag or page tag.

This website does use cookies. Additionally, some of our business partners (for example, advertisers) may use cookies and web beacons as well. Our site has no access to, or control of advertisers’ web cookies or web beacons.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. Please check your browser’s help section for instructions on how to do this.

**Refund policy**

You will be provided with a full refund within 7 days following completion if the article does not follow the guidelines, criteria, and conditions agreed during previous email communication.

**Future Changes**

The details of this policy could be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions with regards to this privacy policy then please contact us.

_If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the  [Contact Us](http://lerablog.org/contact/) form on our website or call +420723758648. _

Last Edited on 2016-22-11
